[Love in the Moonlight, the show
that illuminated the summer of 2016,]
I shall not allow it.
She is mine.
[that left countless iconic lines and scenes]
[had reached a whopping rating of 23.3%]
['Love in the Moonlight' overtakes cable]
[Prince Park Bo Gum takes the world by storm]
['Love in the Moonlight syndrome'
had become a thing of its own.]
[A fan-meeting, carried out as a promise]
If the show reached a rating of over 20%...
[5,000 people in one place!]
the cast promised to hold a fansign in Hanbok.
[Almost a decade ago...]
Thousands of people have come to see it kept.
['Love in the Moonlight' was adored by people]
[And the five youths who made it possible...]
I'm 33 now, so 10 years ago...
[The role that the 23-year-old Bo Gum took on]
I was 23 when I took part in the show.
[Prince Lee Yeong]
It's Lee Yeong. My name.
I'm 27 years old now.
[17-year-old You Jung's role was...]
That means I was 17 at the time.
[Eunuch Sam Nom and crossdresser Ra On]
I, Hong Sam Nom, present to you...
my friendship and devotion.
[25-year-old Jin Young played...]
So, I was 26 years old
[Yoon Seong, the handsome scholar]
or 24, depending on the counting system.
[22-year-old Soo Bin was...]
I think I was 23.
[the snow white maiden, Ha Yeon]
I was counting on meeting you again.
[19-year-old Dong Yeon's part was...]
I was about 20 years old when we filmed it.
[the warrior Byeong Yeon]
You will all fear me.
[Now, after 10 years...]
I can't believe we're...
still working together after a whole decade.
Us five, the five youths
have kept in touch, on good terms.
And I'm proud of that. I really am.
Plans to hang out don't
always work out, you know.
But for us, we always figure out a way
to make time for each other.
[The Moonlight cast has stayed friends...]
We'd work around everyone's schedule.
[for the past 10 years]
We rarely let any one of us miss out.
Well, this 10th anniversary trip...
[Bo Gum took the lead on the trip]
is happening all thanks to Park Bo Gum.
This 10th anniversary trip...
[He had been planning it for a year!]
is a project that I had in mind...
since filming 'Cantabile.'
I liked the idea of the five of us
creating something together.
The number of projects that we had discussed
adds up to around 27,000.
A photoshoot, an OST remake,
and a reality show.
[The anniversary trip was the most loved idea]
I really wanted to make the trip happen.
[A long-time dream,]
I've had it on my mind for a long time.
[the Moonlight cast trip...]
So, with the five of us together,
[starts now!]
I'm very happy to see it happen.
[One fateful hot summer day in August...]
[someone is walking down the road
in the warm sunlight]
[Actor for Lee Yeong, Park Bo Gum]
Hello, everyone.
[At the end of the steep uphill road...]
[Gasp!]
Oh, wow!
[lies a gate, and a surprise beyond it]
[A familiar sight awaits the cast]
No way!
[They are the costumes from 10 years ago!]
[From Prince Lee Yeong's dragon robe]
[to Sam Nom's adorable eunuch robe...]
[and finally, Ra On's beautiful dancing gown]
[the costumes are perfectly preserved
as they were 10 years ago on the set]
[The costume crew treasured these costumes]
Wow, so they really kept these.
[The costumes are bringing back old memories]
They fit right in with the background here.
I can't believe they kept them
in such good condition.
I'm touched.
You seem to be set to a specific mode today.
[The two are in vacation mode]
Yeah, vacation mode.
[They're in a good mood,]
Look, they've got a drone.
[and the right mode]
That's a lot of mosquitoes.
Yeah, some gigantic mosquito, huh?
- I wonder where the set is--oh, what?
- Woah!
- Oh, what?
- Welcome, guys!
- Hello!
- Oh, watch your step.
- Wait...
[Jin Young, as Kim Yoon Seong]
Is there a fee to enter?
[Kim You Jung as Hong Ra On]
How much is it?
- It's free, just for today.
- Oh, my, hello!
[Such bright greetings from
Ra On and Yoon Seong!]
- Oh, wow, it's so pretty!
- Right?
Oh, look what they've got!
Such good memories.
[The red parasol, waiting in the yard]
[10 years ago, under this very parasol,]
[the Yeong & On couple had a secret date!]
Oh, no way!
It's not providing much shade, though.
[The sunlight is strong!]
The sun's not going anywhere.
[Jin Young and You Jung's first encounter...]
So many memories.
[with their costumes from 10 years ago]
These were preserved like this...
- for a decade!
- Wow, that's so cool.
This is how small the robe was?
It felt huge back then.
Yeah, exactly.
[To the 17-year-old Ra On, 10 years ago...]
[the prince seemed so tall and mighty]
I don't remember this gown being this tiny.
[Realizing how small we all were back then]
I don't think I'd fit in it anymore.
I don't think I'd fit in it either.
- We were so little back then.
- We've all bulked up.
They have our pictures over there.
[On the table of the Moonlight crew's
good memories...]
[are photos of the five's younger selves]
What's this?
[A book is on the table as well]
[Lee Yeong's face is on it. What could it be?]
Who drew this?
Oh, it's the book that Ra On wrote!
[It's Ra On's book from the show!]
It's Ra On's book!
[At the end of 'Love in the Moonlight']
In the library, remember?
[Ra On draws Lee Yeong's face
on the novel that she wrote herself]
You said you were writing
the greatest novel ever.
What is this, then?
[The props crew kept it safe
with both of their signatures for 10 years]
They have a secret date at the library, right?
It's actually empty, oops.
It's only visible to those
who are pure of heart.
[The brother and sister...]
Like, on shows like "I am Solo,"
[are having a banter on their way]
it's the male cast that carries the luggage.
- Is that what's happening?
- It's embarrassing to carry this around.
- Oh, look, look!
- Wow, hello, everyone!
[Chae Soo Bin as Jo Ha Yeon]
Hello!
[Kwak Dong Yeon as Kim Byeong Yeon]
Hi!
[The Moonlight cast, reunited at last!]
What are you wearing on your head?
It's too hot!
[Dong Yeon and his mysterious sword]
Where did you get that sword from?
- It's my sword.
- You brought this?
- Yeah.
- What? Is it actually?
[The plastic sword he used for practice]
From the set?
Yeah, the one I used for practice.
- Wow, so cool!
- Oh, I remember.
You still have this?
Well, I actually didn't mean to,
[He stole it from the action school]
but I kind of stole it.
Right, he forgot to return it.
- Oh, he forgot.
- Forgot to give it back?
[The sun is blazing at 37 degrees]
Wow, wait a minute.
It's scorching hot out.
[Byeong Yeon the warrior springs to action]
Not bad, honestly.
[Soo Bin and Dong Yeon...]
Come look at this.
[joins the yard tour]
This is awesome!
- So cool.
- Go put on the bracelets over there.
- See those bracelets?
- What are these?
[Lee Yeong and Ra On's ship name...]
Yeong On bracelets.
[Yeong On themed bracelets]
They prepared five of them.
[The Yeong On bracelet,]
From now on, you are...
[a symbol of the two lovers' devotion]
the most cherished lady in the entire world.
[Now a symbol of the five friends]
Let's make a moon shape.
- Oh, like this? Okay.
- What's that?
- What is that?
- Sorry.
One, two, three.
[They made a full moon with their hands]
Two, three...
Wow, it's been such a long time.
I'm flooded with memories.
Do each of you remember
any stories or scenes from these costumes?
This gown was a dancing gown.
[Ra On's solo dance]
[Lee Yeong's cosmos field finale]
This is from the finale.
Yeah, the robe from the finale.
In the cosmos field.
[Ra On in Yoon Seong's arms]
This one's from when Ra On...
tried to catch a chicken and fell.
[Ha Yeon and Lee Yeong's first encounter]
I think that one's from my first appearance.
I remember wearing it on my first day.
[Byeong Yeon's warrior robe]
Oh, look how worn this is.
It's fake leather, and yet...
Wait, this brand was the rage back then, too?
[Turns out Byeong Yeon
liked to wear Italian leather]
That's hilarious!
- I guess Byeong Yeon was the blueprint.
- May I?
Look at this.
[Warrior Byeong Yeon steals
Yoon Seong the rich kid's expensive bag]
[The man with both a sword and a luxury bag]
He was a true fashionista.
[Joseon trendsetter look]
A Joseon fashionista.
Joseon fashion guru!
[By the end of the trip...]
[the Moonlight cast is back in their costumes]
My name is Hong Ra On, your highness.
You are my whole world, Ra On.
[It's as if they went back in time]
It feels so weird.
- Feels like we've gone back to the past.
- Yeah.
It's like wearing your old school uniform.
- It's a strange feeling.
- Yeah, it's odd.
It feels so weird.
How about we head inside? It'll be cooler.
- Oh, yeah!
- Let's see what it's like inside.
Wait, let's take a photo here.
Ah, yep, yep.
- With these little guys.
- Sure, sure.
[Photo time with their long-lost costumes]
So cute.
[Wink]
[Photo break is over]
- Thank you! - Thank you!
Thanks.
Let's take a selfie, too.
- Oh, okay.
- All together.
Let's take a selfie, too.
- Oh, okay.
- All together.
[Gathering for selfies like second nature]
[Fun fact: Bo Gum loves taking pictures,]
Serial photo-takers, for real.
[and is the photographer of the group.]
One, two, three.
[The Moonlight cast welcomes
all of Bo Gum's photographic whims]
[At last, everyone is entering the lodging]
- Oh, it's cool in here!
- So pretty!
[Located in the middle of a mountain...]
[is our amazing Hanok resort]
[A welcoming living room
for the Moonlight cast...]
[Love in the Moonlight]
Wow, what's all this?
[A welcome pot of lotus tea]
I think it's lotus tea!
[and yakgwa of fond memories]
It's so pretty!
- Let's have a toast.
- Alright.
- I'm so glad we're all together again.
- It feels like we're drinking.
- Here's to a nice vacation!
- A nice vacation.
[A cup of fragrant lotus tea
in wishes for an enjoyable vacation]
- It's quite savory.
- It tastes good.
- What's this? Are we allowed to open it?
- I think it's a present.
[A welcome gift on the table]
Love in the Moonlight: Redrawn?
Open!
That's a big watch.
Oh, what's this?
[A film camera, a camcorder, and portable fans]
Oh, look, fans!
- Wow, a camera!
- It's a camera.
We can take pictures with this now.
- I'll take the camcorder, then.
- The camcorder?
[What memories will this camera hold?]
I'll take the camera, then.
[Preview of the camcorder]
Is it working?
[The Moonlight cast's
adorable activities will be recorded]
You have to do a little dance, like so.
Tomato pasta.
If you don't play, you lose,
rock, paper, scissors!
[The portable fans are one for each]
I'll just take a fan.
- I like them.
- The fan...
[They turn the fans on to find...]
Let me see.
[that the wings reveal texts!]
Look, right there!
- Look, right there!
- Wow, wow, wow!
- A ferocious herbivore...
- Wow, technology sure has advanced.
[The words on the fans are...]
Wow, technology sure has advanced.
[Ferocious Herbivore]
Like a ferocious herbivore.
[School President]
Vibes of a school president.
[Youngest Uncle]
I'd say... like a youngest uncle?
[Dr. Oh Eun Young]
Like Dr. Oh Eun Young.
[The nicknames they gave each other
during the pre-interview]
[Perfect Tease]
Just perfect to tease.
[Only the name giver knows who owns each fan]
Youngest uncle?
- Youngest uncle...
- Dr. Oh Eun Young, too?
[Youngest uncle, Dr. Oh, school president,
perfect tease, ferocious herbivore]
A school president, a perfect tease...
A perfect tease... and a ferocious herbivore?
[Time to find the owner of each fan]
A ferocious herbivore.
[Ferocious herbivore]
This one's obvious.
Who is it?
- Isn't it Soo Bin?
- Me?
- Am I ferocious?
- Well, no, but...
She's obviously a herbivore...
but who called her ferocious?
Like a ferocious herbivore.
She's very good to tease
because she has a big reaction.
[Loud but harmless]
But if you listen to what she's saying...
she just isn't very good at threatening.
So why am I a ferocious herbivore?
- You're doing it right now.
- Look at yourself.
- The way she's asking, right?
- Yeah, like, "why am I a ferocious..."
[A sneak peek at the ferocious herbivore]
Eat it with rice...
[Being loud]
Quiet down!
[Just one more chance, please!]
Give me another chance!
[Talking about a restaurant visit
after a photoshoot for a poster]
Yeah, I think it was
after that poster photoshoot.
Wait, I was at that photoshoot, too.
Why didn't I get invited?
[Turns out it was a different day]
I guess it was a different day.
[Isn't afraid to talk, but isn't scary either]
That was such a fast remark.
No, seriously.
Who's Dr. Oh Eun Young, then?
Wait, isn't that You Jung?
[Is You Jung's nickname 'Dr. Oh Eun Young'?]
It feels right, yeah.
Is that who I am?
[Or is it 'School President'?]
Maybe You Jung is the school president.
[No one is agreeing]
I don't think so.
[So who is which?]
What if I'm Dr. Oh Eun Young?
- Take this, then.
- Are you Dr. Oh?
[You Jung: Dr. Oh Eun Young]
I'm Dr. Oh Eun Young?
Who gave me this nickname?
[Jin Young did it]
It was me.
- You're the school president.
- Oh, really?
[Bo Gum: School President]
It's you.
But I want to be Dr. Oh Eun Young.
Dr. Oh Eun Young.
She can scold even those older than her.
There's just this aura about her.
[Rascal #1, ordering a diet coke]
Do you have diet coke?
It'll trick your body...
[Dr. Oh, considerate of the rascals' health]
into thinking it didn't get any sugar.
[Did research on what they need for dinner]
I looked up all the ingredients for baeksuk.
[Rascal #2, who has a different menu in mind]
I want potato fritters. Can we just have that?
That, or kimchi pancake.
Alright, we can do potato fritters.
[Dr. Oh presents an easy-breezy solution]
And if we have time, kimchi pancake as well.
[Soo Bin named Bo Gum]
Bo Gum is... like a school president.
I'm probably the school president.
[Everyone admits he's the school president]
I'm just inclined to guide our group.
This whole thing was your idea, anyway.
[President Park's feat #1: planning the trip]
Exactly.
[President Park's feat #2: a spoon of romance]
This feels like a photoshoot in itself.
I hope our friendship lasts forever.
- May I buy this?
- Nope.
[President Park's feat #3: no wasting money]
But why? Just one, please?
- No, don't buy it.
- But why?
- I want some thrill.
- Oh, you want a thrill?
Nuh-uh.
[Can't sit by and watch the cast be reckless]
Too dangerous.
[Is Jin Young the youngest uncle?]
Just take this.
It's not him!
[Take it]
The youngest uncle...
[You Jung named Dong Yeon 'Youngest Uncle']
What, me?
I came up with it.
Oh, really? So he's the great uncle, or what?
Dong Yeon is a jokester.
- Boo!
- Boo.
The three seniors.
[Senior #1, #2, #3]
The three seniors?
[Likes to make fun of people
like the youngest uncle of the family]
Toodles, stragglers!
One of us will have to give up a drumstick.
I can give it up.
- Me, too.
- I don't have to eat one.
Alright, then, can I have three?
Sexy dynamite!
[The shame is for his friends to bear]
[Lastly, Jin Young is the perfect tease]
Over there, 'perfect tease'.
- That's me?
- Yeah.
- But why?
- Well, you are good to poke fun at.
- You're really fun to tease.
- Am I?
These guys...
They love to make fun of me.
And the center of all evil...
is Dong Yeon and You Jung.
[Doesn't even deny it]
I do tease him a lot.
He really makes me put myself on trial.
I keep wondering how much he'd put up with me.
[Source of all evil #1 and #2]
Well? What am I?
[Unfortunately the 'Perfect Tease'
is seated between these two]
There's no explanation needed, is there?
Clearly something went wrong
somewhere along the way.
- I think I know where it went wrong.
- Well? Tell me.
- I think it started with ghosts.
- Oh, true.
I'm scared of ghosts.
One time, they came over to my place.
It was a duplex with a basement.
He started to say that he kept hearing sounds.
So we all joined in on it.
Like, "I think I actually hear something."
He was terrified.
Then, Jin Young asked me to stay over.
- Just how scared were you?
- But...
Isn't everyone afraid of ghosts?
[I dare any ghost lovers to come forth!]
Seriously, does anyone like ghosts?
Who likes ghosts anyway?
Well, nobody likes them, of course.
[Seriously contemplating]
But...
I guess it is scary, if you think about it.
Imagine you're all alone.
[Snicker]
And that place...
[The president is trying hard to comfort him]
did have a spooky vibe to it.
- He's being an empath!
- But that place was kind of spooky, yeah.
- Yeah, that's true.
- It was.
You gave a proper goodbye
when you moved out, right?
No, they moved together.
Don't say that.
[The two pinnacles of evil, making their move]
Oh, it's the same ghost, then?
- Like, in his house, now?
- Yeah, the same one.
You'll be fine.
You're sleeping with us tonight.
So now we change and go eat, right?
[They're changing to go rafting]
Yeah, let's change.
But, like, rafting and stuff...
won't get you wet or anything, right?
- Of course you'll get wet.
- Yeah, you will.
- Why?
- It's a water sport, duh.
We'll be in the water.
- You might fall off the raft, too.
- The river here in Hongcheon is rough.
- That won't do.
- What's wrong? Didn't pack your swimming suit?
No, it's not that.
- What is it, then?
- Well, the water...
- Are you scared?
- Of falling in!
- You're scared of water?
- Of falling in.
[There's no way he's not getting teased]
[Dying of laughter]
Well, Bo Gum is...
- He's a great swimmer.
- Yeah?
- He'll save you for sure.
- Oh, okay. Okay.
- Don't worry too much about it.
- I believe you.
[He is indeed a perfect tease]
This is gold.
- Don't worry about it.
- There are four of us here.
[Oh Eun Young(27) / Ph.D.]
What are you worried about?
We have life vests, too.
[The Moonlight cast are ready to go]
Shall we go now?
Shall we?
Why not take another photo before we go?
[Moonlight photographer, on the move]
It's going to turn out backlit.
How about now?
[Snap snap with a beating heart
before the vacation officially starts]
[Bo Gum's choice of restaurant for lunch]
Is this the place you told me about?
Yes.
They've got all sorts of stuff on the menu!
- Boneless short rib sounds good.
- Boneless short rib!
Octopus on a griddle must be good, too.
Oh, and cold noodles as a palate cleanser.
[And potato pancakes, You Jung's choice]
Oh, potato pancakes!
- One potato pancake, please.
- Alright.
Did you answer this in the pre-interview, too?
So who do you think would get married first?
- What? No!
- They didn't ask me that.
[All four except Bo Gum have no idea]
They asked that?
- They didn't ask you?
- No.
So? What did you say?
- First place was You Jung.
- Me?
First place was You Jung.
[You Jung, the youngest, the fastest to marry?]
Me?
- Wait, why me?
- Yeah, why her?
[The others are surprised to hear this, too]
Why me?
Why, why me?
I'm the youngest here!
- Why?
- Well, I think you're the most likely...
[The clever youngest]
to meet a good person and get married.
Then who do you think would be the last?
The last, huh?
[Gaze goes towards the oldest of them all]
Wait, no, not him!
[Why is he looking at me?]
[Finishes him off with another glance]
[Perfect tease]
Why? What, why me?
[Just making fun of the eldest]
Oh, I'm just kidding.
I don't think anyone's going to marry too late.
It'd feel so weird, though.
- If any of us got married, you know.
- Yeah.
[You Jung would be married by then?]
So I'd just be married in 10 years?
Because I'd be the one to marry the fastest?
Yeah, I guess.
It just came to me all of a sudden.
Like, I wish we all ended up as neighbors.
Oh, we did have that talk last time.
[Friends you'd still want after 10 more years]
We'd babysit each other's kids.
We could have vacations together.
So by our 20th anniversary trip
we'd all be accompanied by babies?
How old would we be by then?
[10 years later, You Jung would be 37]
You Jung would be in her 30s.
Mid 30s, actually.
I'd be 46.
Woah.
I wish you longevity.
[Heartfelt advice for the eldest]
You need to take good care of your health.
Actually, look at the way he's dressed.
[He looks like a typical middle-aged-hiker]
We might be riding Jin Young's boat today.
[The boat we'll be rafting on may well be his]
Wear these shades.
[He looks like a rafting guide]
[Item added]
[Boat captain core]
Oh, captain, captain!
- It suits you. Captain.
- Captain Jin.
That's hilarious.
[Right on time, today's lunch has arrived]
Oh, thank you.
Appreciate it.
[The main dish, boneless short ribs,
presentable and pink]
[Current time 10:30]
Grilling meat for breakfast. How luxurious.
It looks so good.
[The meat has already turned golden brown]
Looks so delicious. Salty and savory.
[Full of plump octopus]
Wow.
[Octopus on a griddle, looking tasty as ever]
The octopus looks so good.
[And a crispy and moist potato pancake]
This is a lot of food!
[Photos are obligatory even before a meal]
Let's take a photo.
Everyone, look here.
One, two, three.
[First meal of the trip is a feast!]
Perfect.
La la, looks so good!
- Let's enjoy this food!
- Thank you for the meal!
Let's hit it.
[The short rib wins the first bite,
dipped in sauce]
- Mm!
- Is it good?
[Taste so good it awes you]
Gangwon beef is the best beef.
Is it that good?
[Eldest Jin Young takes a bite]
Wow.
[Just as tasty for their first meal]
So good.
It's really good.
[Put some meat on some perilla leaves]
[and take a well-balanced bite]
[You Jung is having the time of her life]
[Chomp]
[Muk-Bo Gum binges on meat ssams as well]
Do you remember the day
we did the full script reading?
[Dong Yeon was a late recruit]
I wasn't there.
Yeah, I remember. He wasn't there.
I just remembered what I was wearing that day.
No way! What were you wearing?
A white shirt.
I think I wore a white shirt, too.
I was wearing white, too!
Hey, I think I did, too.
[They all wore white as if they'd planned it]
Yeah, I was wearing white, too. At home.
[Dong Yeon stayed true
to the dress code as well, it seems]
I was in that phase at the time.
[Original director of Love in the Moonlight]
I hated director Seong Yoon.
Why?
[They had worked together from Puberty Medley]
I'd already worked with him, so we were close.
So I thought I'd get to audition
for 'Love in the Moonlight' as well.
But he didn't call me in.
So I gave him a call asking
why he didn't call me in.
What did he say?
"You don't need an audition, I know you."
He said no.
So I went straight to the office to audition.
[That's how badly he wanted the role]
I told him I wanted to play Byeong Yeon.
[But he didn't get cast for the role]
But I still didn't get it.
So I was cursing him at home.
[Guess he wasn't in normal white clothes]
Yeah, in white mourning clothes, the full pack.
And then...
I took back all of the curses
I put on him once I got the part.
[I took everything back since we became a team]
Reversed the curse.
Oh, do you guys remember?
I used to call everyone "uncle"
because I was so young,
and I felt awkward having to say "oppa,"
so I just didn't use it.
I would just say "hyung," or just "mister."
Remember I used to call you
Mr. Bo Gum and Mr. You Jung?
But then, people wanted me to change it.
They told me to call him Bo Gum oppa.
So he became the only person
I'd ever use "oppa" to, at the time.
Just what happened back then.
- I'm honored.
- Except for my real brother, of course.
[Bo Gum took the honor ten years ago]
That makes me kind of glad.
I'm craving something like makgeolli.
Let's grab some from the supermarket later.
I'm on vacation mode today.
- Oh, right. Of course.
- I'm going to get hammered today.
[Shocked]
[An unfathomable concept to Park, the nice kid]
Look at his face!
Did you ever drink with us, You Jung?
- We've drunk, yeah. Lots.
- That day...
Did I not drink that day?
When the three of us met?
There was that day where we went off the rails.
In Yongsan, remember?
Wasn't it a spontaneous thing?
[Bo Gum, You Jung, and Dong Yeon showed up]
Yeah, it was. It was.
But I think you contacted everyone here.
- Yeah, I joined in late.
- And all of a sudden...
- Bo Gum really let himself go that day.
- Right, I remember.
He was begging us to go bar hopping.
Yeah, we stayed out so late that night.
I think that was the first time
I've ever stayed out that late.
I think that was
the most you've ever drank, too.
[The most Bo Gum has ever drunk is a pint]
Yeah, I had a full pint, right?
What surprised me more was that there were
places still open at such an hour.
[He didn't know about the Yongsan nightlife]
Bo Gum...
- And you were...
- That's Yongsan to you.
I'm never outside at those hours.
Thank you for enjoying spending time with us.
[New horizons...]
Of course I do.
[are best explored with the Moonlight cast]
It was a historical moment, yes.
We're going to need lots of strength
for the upcoming day and a half.
[Bo Gum prepared gifts for everyone]
First off, have one of these.
[Red ginseng extract for energy!]
Take these to re-energize.
- Oh, it's 'Everytime'.
- Thank you!
Thanks.
Let's get our energy levels up and go rafting!
Yes sir!
[Power up!]
I really like how easy and revitalizing it is.
Now, let's go rafting!
- Let's go!
- Off we go!
[Full bellies call for a refreshing rafting!]
- Go, go! - Thank you for the amazing meal!
[Clear skies,]
The weather is perfect.
What kind of tree is that?
[and pretty flowers]
Oh, how pretty!
It's a Rose of Sharon.
- Oh, really?
- Wow!
Hey, what's that over there?
I want to go play there.
I want to dive in!
[The river is finally in sight]
Oh, look! Life vests.
[Nervous]
Would this be enough for you?
[The moment of doom approaches]
Or do you need them to be thicker?
- No, not at all. I'm fine...
- Uh, yes, you do.
[Arrived at last!]
Oh, you're still scared, aren't you?
I've never done anything like this before.
Thank you!
- Hello!
- Good morning!
I'll be guiding the five of you for the day.
- Nice to meet you.
Please, take special care of this one.
[Scaredy-cat(35): scared of water]
What, me?
[Life vests on first and foremost]
Before we go, put on the life vests behind you.
So, about the course that we'll be taking...
[Checking the difficulty for the eldest baby]
How "thrilling" would it be?
- On a scale from one to ten?
- Yeah, on a scale to ten.
[A seven or eight out of ten!]
Around seven or eight.
[Shocked]
Seven or eight.
[Go on ahead, guys... I'll just see myself out]
[Taking a ride to the boarding point]
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You have such broad shoulders.
Wow, you look totally ripped right now.
Sir, how is Hongcheon river this year?
Will we fall in the water?
How long is the ride?
About one and a half hours.
[More excitement just means more questions]
[The rafting site
is getting closer by the minute]
Wait, the river is really rapid!
Where? Let me see!
[The current appears to be rapid]
Yeah, it's flowing fast!
The current is faster than expected!
Mr. Jin Young's thoughts
must be racing right now.
[Jin Young's race against fate has also begun]
It'll be fine.
We're here.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for the ride!
Wow! This looks like so much fun!
[Hongcheon river rafting]
[Boating along the twisting river...]
[Hongcheon's famed water sports activity]
[Ten years ago, Ra On fell from a boat...]
Y-your highness!
[and Lee Yeong leaped to the rescue]
Your highness!
[As this is a 10th anniversary trip...]
[all five friends will be jumping in
without a care in the world!]
[The episode was filmed under surveillance
of experts, following safety rules]
[The Moonlight Five are on board!]
Strap your foot in, and let the other one hang.
[Ship Hongcheon river Moonlight sets sail!]
Let's start.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go catch a shark!
Let's see if your voice is loud enough,
and if you row well enough!
- Yes, sir!
- Forward! One, two!
- Three, four!
- One, two!
[Still has a long way to row]
One, two!
- Three, four!
- One, two!
- And cease.
When I say "cease,"
the paddles return to your knees.
- On my knees.
- On my knees!
- Why am I getting a preview of the army life?
- Take a knee!
[Fun fact: Dong Yeon is to be enlisted
in three weeks from this moment]
On the left! Your voice was too small.
[You three! Louder!]
The left side was being too quiet, right?
- The left side? Yeah!
- Yes!
- They weren't loud enough.
- Boo!
- Boo! Boo!
[Soo Bin, report!]
You hear that, Soo Bin?
[Private Herbivore's just sunshine and daisies]
Do you want to take a dip first?
Oh, no, no, we're fine.
Now, the third person on the left side
will give us a good chant!
[Jin Young's chant]
- Oh, me? - So, that's you, right there.
It goes "one, two," and we're off!
[Squad on a mission!]
One, two!
- Three, four!
- One, two!
[Synchronized rowing at its best]
Three, four!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- One, two...
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Cease!
Now, moving on to the person right in front.
[The smaller the voice, the faster the dive]
The one with the smallest voice dives first.
Let's go, number two.
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
- One, two!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
[The cue to row is on "three, four"...]
Three, four!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
[Falter]
One! Two!
Three, four!
Her paddling is off!
[Just loud and wrong...]
She's paddling at "one, two!"
[our dear Private Herbivore]
The rhythm is awful!
- Totally wrong...
- Just give me one more chance!
Okay, let's go!
I don't think another chance
will make any difference.
- No, sir! I can do it, sir!
- Let's go!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
- Three, four.
- One, two!
- Three, four!
[She's laughing, too]
One, two...
- Three, four!
- One! Two!
- Cease.
I heard you well enough. Now, moving on!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
[Loud and ringing]
One! Two!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
- Is this all you've got, Marine?
[Navy force activated]
- One! Two! - Three, four!
- One! Two!
- Three, four!
One-two!
[Private Gwak on the frontier]
Three, four!
- One-two!
- Three, four!
[Rowing at a right angle]
One-two!
- Three, four!
- One-two!
Three, four!
[Sergeant Kim is here!]
Sea! Waves!
- Sea! Waves!
- Three, four!
Sea! Waves!
[The short-timer sergeant is the loudest]
Three, four!
- Sea! Waves!
- Three, four!
Oof, my throat is so sore.
How am I going to reenact the show now?
Yeah, a sore throat is no joke.
[Team A: Bo Gum, Soo Bin, Jin Young]
The left side is team A,
[Team B: Dong Yeon, You Jung]
and on the right is team B.
From now on, both teams A and B
will climb onto the rail.
- The rail?
- Railing? Oh, here?
Yes, now rise!
[Suddenly excited]
I think we're fighting!
No way!
One, two, three.
Wait!
[It's hard just standing upright]
You can hold onto me.
[Grasp]
Oh, my gosh!
[Team B is steady and successful]
How do I climb on top?
That's it, yeah.
Watch out for the center.
[Making a ruckus]
No, don't let go of me!
You'll need to let go.
[Team A isn't doing so hot]
But sir!
If you want stability,
just hold on to those two.
That's true.
Shoulder to shoulder! Go shoulder to shoulder.
Shoulder to shoul-der!
One of the teams is going to fall.
[One of the teams will fall?]
Just one team.
Now, team A will slowly crouch down.
- Team A, crouching...
- Crouching...
- And as they rise back up, team B will crouch.
- Okay.
We'll repeat this until one of you falls.
Let's go! One!
[Wobble wobble]
Two!
- Hey, wait.
- Two!
[Teetering and tottering...]
[and then she gives a deep bow!]
No, don't give a deep bow!
[Tumble]
What's up with that?
Do it again, come on. Let's redo that.
Sir, y-you almost threw me overboard!
[Just full of joy and whimsy]
[Herbivore down!]
You okay?
You have to get back up.
Let's try again.
- Until someone falls in.
- Wait, wait.
Is this right?
Take it slow. Try to stand.
[Back on the edge]
Slow and steady.
- You can grab onto me.
- You go first.
[The never-ending seesaw starts again]
Let's start from the top. Team A, squat.
- Crouch...
- Again, now, one!
- One...
- Two!
- Two...
- One!
[The boat wobbles again]
One, two!
- One, two!
[Good-bye]
[The honor of taking the first dip
goes to team A]
[Ugh!]
[Nice play!]
We did it! We survived!
[Sputter sputter]
Toodles, stragglers!
[The soggy stragglers]
We're leaving you!
We're leaving without you!
Are you alright?
[Not at all, actually...]
Oh, thank you.
- Oh, it got in my mouth.
- I really tried...
[The stragglers are back on board]
[Bo Gum swiftly climbs back on]
Wait, is that yours?
[You Jung tries to help Soo Bin up]
Turn your back to me.
Like this?
Ow, my crotch!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
[The life vest straps go on the legs]
I forgot the strap went on the legs.
- Again, again.
- Wouldn't it hurt?
No, I'll just hold it.
Oh, okay.
[Rushing to help]
Won't it hurt?
Yeah, she's holding it. One, two, three!
[A real big catch comes with a wail]
It's like we caught a fish.
Just hauling her up like a catch.
[Guys, what about me?]
[Team A, back on board screaming]
Do we get back into position?
- Yes, back in position.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, then. Again...
[Moving forward!]
Forward!
Louder, one, two!
- Three! Four!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- One! Two!
[Morales are high]
Three, four!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- One-two!
- Three-four!
- Three, four!
[Splish splash]
- One, two! - Three, four!
- One-two!
- Three-four!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- One-two!
[Private Gwak of pure passion]
- One, two! - Three! Four!
- One-two!
- Three-four!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
And cease!
Hey, excuse me.
Could you not splash me with water, please?
[Private Gwak is too passionate]
You were practically shoveling it onto me.
I got too eager.
- I mean, I don't want to be the one to dive.
- That's so funny.
The right-side team has only two people,
but you're way better than the left.
You guys are good at rowing.
We are, aren't we?
- Boo!
- Boo-oo!
The three seniors.
The three seniors?
[Senior #1(33), #2(32), #3(35)]
[Being in your 30s is considered old here]
We can't even deny it, it's so frustrating.
- Forward! One, two!
- Three, four!
[The energetic 20-year-olds...]
- One, two! - Three, four!
[and the 30s, trying their best]
- Cease!
- Cease.
On my knees.
Do you like diving?
- What?
- Diving. Do you like to dive?
Uh, no?
Up ahead, 12 o'clock, you see all those boats?
- Yes.
- That tower of boats?
- We're going to dive from it.
- Wow!
We can dive? Oh, wow.
What?
[In the middle of the Hongcheon river...]
[is a thrilling diving spot!]
[Safety guards]
Oh, it's a stack of boats?
Yes, that's the highest we can stack them.
Is that about three meters high?
[It's about three meters tall]
Almost, yeah.
No way I can jump from that.
What? That's nothing!
[The episode was filmed under surveillance...]
Put the paddles away in the center,
[of experts, following safety rules]
and slowly get off the boat.
Hello, everyone.
The one with the loudest voice...
[First up is Bo Gum]
will go first.
- Oh, first?
- Ah, well.
- Stand in front of me.
- Oh, this looks fun!
Forward.
[Heart racing]
Jump far out, okay?
I'm going to do it.
[A running start followed by a cool jump]
[His diving form is just as good
as when he dived to save Ra On]
[President Park makes a great starting dive]
[Maximum refreshment]
It's so much fun!
[You Jung is the next diver]
Next up!
[Leaping and pouncing]
Take it easy.
She's like a little kid.
Like an excited kid.
[Little You Jung has no fear!]
Just aim for the farthest jump you can do.
Far?
Yeah, jump as far as you can.
[Not a glimpse of hesitation to be found]
[Unlike when she was a eunuch,
helplessly drowning in water...]
[You Jung is enjoying her refreshing dive!]
Oh, it's so cold!
[While You Jung is enjoying her swim...]
[Private Gwak has bravely made his climb]
- Go, Gwak Dong Yeon!
Oh, so cool!
[Private Gwak does a flip!]
- That's awesome!
- That was so cool!
- Seriously, that was amazing.
- Wow, what was that?
[Feeling awesome]
How did you do that?
Just do a flip.
Like, flip out!
[The prince tries his hand at it, too]
You can do it!
Come on!
What was that?
[Took a wrong step]
[Something seems off]
[Just ended up like some guy
who fell by accident]
[The prince turns out to be a great jester]
My knees folded weird...
[Cackles]
That's just falling over forward, no?
Did you get a good look at the water?
[Nod nod]
Next!
[All that's left are Soo Bin and Jin Young]
Why are you both shying away?
- Are you going to?
- It's fun!
Can I just not jump?
[Whispers of the Devil]
You don't have to, but just climb up here.
It's really fun, just try!
I still have to climb up there?
[Soo Bin musters up the courage and climbs up]
It's hot, so be careful.
Oh, no, this won't work.
Soo Bin, trust me, it's not scary at all.
You can't come back down anyway.
- I want to go back down.
- You can't!
[Soo Bin is already
past the point of no return]
Yeah, no way back.
Just scooch on over to the edge, come on.
[Pins and needles]
Just to the edge.
And now, from there,
it's safest to jump as far as you can. Go on.
[Glance]
[Tremble tremble]
Oh, her legs are shaking!
It's alright!
Go, Chae Soo Bin!
Far, jump far!
[Up and down, up and down]
Come on!
Eyes forward.
I-I can't do it!
It's scarier to climb down.
[Dr. Oh Eun Young's solution]
Push her. Push her! Safely.
[Rejected]
No way!
Oh, can I push her?
- No!
- If you don't jump in five seconds,
I'll push you off. Five...
Four...
[I have to jump before I get pushed!]
Five... Four... Three...
[You can do it, Soo Bin!]
Four... Three... Two...
[With a sharp yelp...]
Two...
[The herbivore jumps in the water!]
[Pop!]
[Turns out, she's aquatic as well]
[Good job, Chae Soo Bin!]
- It worked.
- She jumped as soon as he said he'd push her.
[With Soo Bin's success,
the air is thick with excitement]
- What happened?
- Your hair!
[Only one who isn't so jolly]
You can do it!
[The eldest was even scared of rafting]
Rafting won't get you wet or anything, right?
- Of course you'll get wet.
- Yeah, you will.
Why?
[The youngsters have already
jumped with no fear at all...]
[Shaking and trembling]
[He'd sometimes laugh along...]
[and he'd sigh...]
[but now he's on the diving board!]
Don't worry.
You can do it!
W-wait a minute. Just wait.
[His legs have gone weak already]
Get up.
Ow, it's hot.
It's fun, see? Be confident!
[Isn't even listening]
No, wait...
Wait, wait. This...
[This is way too tall for him to handle]
This is hard.
- Come on.
- You can do this!
Big brother! Eldest brother!
Show us a cool trick!
Let me breathe, okay?
He's adorable.
[Heavy is the burden of being the eldest]
Sure, breathe in deep.
Cute!
Should I do the countdown for him, too?
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- Yes!
- Five!
- Alright, alright!
[Guys, please, calm down]
Four!
I-I need to do my breathing exercise.
[What a cutie.]
Okay, I'm going.
[There's nowhere else to run...]
[The little ones are watching me!]
Eldest brother! Show us a cool trick!
[I am the eldest of the Moonlight cast!]
[He makes a beautiful dive
by overcoming his fear!]
[The eldest could show courage
thanks to his younger peers' encouragement]
[Tries to swim]
[While the eldest is proud of himself...]
[Bo Gum, You Jung and Dong Yeon
have all climbed to the top again]
[The three friends
had so much chemistry ten years ago]
- Grueling training...
- I'd hope so.
Scooch forward a little more.
[The Jahyeondang Three are diving together]
Yes, forward.
All at once. One, two, three!
[The Jahyeondang Three soars freely]
[A three-person jump makes thrice the thrill!]
[A group dive makes you laugh]
[After a successful dive...]
We'll head straight to the endpoint now.
- Yes, sir!
- Yes, sir.
[Swimming towards the end point]
Let's race to see who's the fastest swimmer!
Sounds good.
Ready, set, go!
[Tweedledum and Tweedledee]
Same difference.
[The Passionate Private Gwak returns]
[The Moonlight cast,
channeling their inner child]
[I'm just going to go ahead]
[The obvious fastest swimmer is...]
[this happy seal]
[I wonder if they're following me well?]
[Smooth sailing,
even with You Jung and Soo Bin attached]
We're coming to save you!
[Come, come!]
Why don't we all hold hands?
Let's all hold hands while we swim.
Try lying on your back.
[Hand in hand, floating serenely]
Let's lie down.
Kick your feet, come on.
Who's leading?
Jin Young is.
Why was there a long pause?
Hey, Bo Gum, do a flip!
[Will he try again, this time from the boat?]
Yeah, do a flip!
- I don't think I can.
- No, no.
Just jump, and flip!
[After rafting and cooling down
from the summer heat...]
[land ahoy!]
Oh, there's a spooky story about this place.
Have you heard about it? I doubt you have.
- We haven't.
- Let's tell them. We have to.
[An urban legend about the Hongcheon river]
So, if you follow the river downstream...
- that's the Palbong mountain.
- Yes?
- See that pointy peak on the far left?
- Yeah.
- That one, on the left?
- Oh, yeah.
It's called that because it has eight peaks.
At the very edge...
[Gaksi Rock at the edge of Palbong mountain]
there's a boulder called the Gaksi Rock.
- Gaksi?
- Like, a newlywed bride.
So this Gaksi Rock is strangely
always shrouded in a veil of darkness.
There are many pensions around there,
and every night, men go there and drown.
They say a woman there keeps
luring men in with her singing.
- Telling them to come in.
[The Gaksi Rock ghost who even sings well]
By the time you snap out of it...
The water is already up to your neck.
Oppa, why are you so quiet?
Jin Young oppa became so quiet.
[Cowardly Hyung / 35, weak to water and ghosts]
- He's scared right now.
- It'll appear after a short walk from here.
- I'll come back later.
- Okay.
[Staggering]
Oh, wait a minute.
[The cowardly hyung's legs give out]
- No, this is weird. - I'm sorry.
[Ending with the legend of Gaksi Rock...]
Ah, that's so funny.
[Rafting ends]
- Good job, everyone. - Good job.
[Time to go grocery shopping after rafting]
Let's go grocery shopping.
[Bo Gum > Soo Bin]
Is Soo Bin's ear okay?
[Soo Bin went to the hospital for ear pain]
She's fine, but she's going just in case.
[Only four people are going shopping]
- She's going? - So just the four of us?
- Yes. The ingredients...
- Ingredients for baeksuk?
- Since we're having baeksuk.
- Is it baeksuk?
[Back in the Moonlight Drawn by Clouds days!]
There was a scene where we ate chicken.
- Yes. The scene where we eat baeksuk.
- Right?
- I didn't know he was the Crown Prince.
- Right.
[The scene at the bench in Jahyundang]
You even cursed at him for not greeting you.
[The five friends will enjoy it together]
Sorry. It's because so hot now.
It's hot right now.
The things that go into baeksuk...
[The main chef who searched in advance]
- Did you find it? - I found it.
Oh, yes.
Water, leeks, garlic, onion,
whole pepper, jujubes, and salt.
That should be enough.
And to eat with it...
Watermelon. Green onion kimchi.
[Side menus are also ready]
Let's buy chives and make seasoned chives.
Can you make us shredded potato pancakes?
[You Jung made them for the members before]
Those potato pancakes were so good.
[The unforgettable You Jung style pancakes]
Shredded potato pancakes. Shredded.
- Right. Should I make them?
- Yes.
I thought you might not want them
since we had potato pancakes earlier.
Potato pancakes, kimchi pancakes,
or we could make spicy noodles.
- Spicy noodles.
- Then can you pick just one?
[Chef You Jung confirms two types of pancakes]
I'll make potato and kimchi pancakes.
[A refreshing summer day with blue skies]
[A drive that makes you hum along]
You seem very excited.
Is the child free?
The child.
Are you saying it is free of charge?
[Arriving at the market]
We're here.
- Thank you.
- Let's go!
- So hot!
- Hello.
- It's so hot.
Let's go.
Can I buy this?
I really like this.
- No.
- Why? Just one.
- Don't buy it.
- Aw, why?
- Just one.
- Don't buy it.
You're really not buying it for me?
- No.
- You're so heartless.
- We just need two chickens.
- Don't buy things like that.
Two chickens?
[Buying ingredients for baeksuk first]
Let's see,
[+ Chicken 1 + Chicken 2]
- Right? - Yeah.
[ Chicken, Seasoning,
Veggies, Side dishes, Snacks, Drinks]
He's letting me buy this.
What about this?
[Like a dad who never buys toys]
Put it back.
We don't need soybean paste,
but we need to buy salt.
- I'll go get some pepper.
- Whole peppercorns.
[Shopping goes smoothly under You Jung's lead]
I'll mix green onions, perilla, and chives.
- Making potato pancakes too might be too hard.
- What? Potato pancakes?
I think I can make them quickly.
- Here are the potatoes.
- We need to buy green onions.
They've pre-portioned the potatoes like this.
I can slice these up in no time.
[Potatoes purchased]
I think four will be enough.
[??? Bo Gum heading somewhere alone]
Hehe.
[Caught wandering the snack aisle]
Again, right before a meal.
Come here. Over here.
Give it to me.
Let me have it first.
- Two?
- No. Just get one.
Here's the watermelon.
- Oh, okay!
- We have to eat this.
- This is delicious too.
- No, no. Come here. No.
[Worried he won't eat his dinner...]
No, you have to eat dinner.
Seriously, what's with you guys?
- It's good.
- You need to eat a proper meal.
[The snack crackdown squad fails]
I'm telling you, he won't eat dinner now.
Hello.
Where are you from?
[Starting a solo skit while the guys are away]
I think they're filming something here.
I'm here to pick up a potato mallangi today.
I'll sneak it onto the counter
so Bo Gum doesn't see.
[The youngest buys a mallangi
while the guys buy snacks]
[Enough food for three days]
Did we buy too much?
The cart looks like a 3-day trip.
- I know.
- Let's go.
[Current time 16:30 Shopping finished]
[Heading back to the lodge with happy hearts]
[Rustling]
Isn't that an Akppu?
[Glancing, Let me see]
This isn't Wapu. It's just a mallangi.
You didn't let me buy it...
[Curious now that she bought it]
Let me touch it.
- I've never seen this before.
- "Teacher," haha.
[Experiencing new things thanks to her]
So this is what it's like.
Yujin-i?
- What?
- Huh?
It's not even Yujin-li.
- Right.
- Why Yujin-i?
Yujin-li? Yujin-i?
[Suddenly getting scared...]
I'm already scared.
Why is that scary?
No, don't you think we saw something wrong
all of us together?
[Worried they're all possessed]
Something changed.
We can drop you off there on the way.
At Gaksi Rock.
Is Yujin at Gaksi Rock?
- Is the bride's name Yujin?
- Yes, Ms. Yujin.
Oppa, I'm Yujin.
I think those campers are amazing.
Despite the heat and everything.
- You said you've tried camping, right?
- Yes.
Camping used to be my hobby.
- You went on that pilgrimage is amazing.
- Truly.
[ An 800 km journey
to Santiago de Compostela, Spain.]
[With just a backpack]
Roughly how many days did you walk?
[You Jung walked the pilgrimage for a month]
I walked for exactly 33 days.
So you just keep walking until find
like a dormitory? Then you eat and sleep?
Yeah.
Usually, the people who start on the same day
as I did end up arriving around the same time.
You meet along the way.
We meet on the way and often eat together.
So people often become close friends.
Even though you mostly walk alone.
So, being alone in those vast fields
and the wilderness...
That feeling is really great.
It makes me feel truly free.
I can feel that I'm experiencing true freedom.
[Arrived at the lodge]
It's so green and lush.
- Oh my.
- What's this?
- They prepared a snack for us.
- Corn!
[Relaxing with corn in the late afternoon]
It's seasoned so well.
Hyung, if you don't mind...
Who wants a beer?
[Of course]
Can I lie down on your lap for a bit?
Who wants a beer?
Do you want some corn beer?
- Is it cold?
- Do you want to share this?
Corn with corn beer is a great combo.
But were you really scared earlier?
Of course.
- When? While rafting?
- I was terrified.
But you seemed to enjoy it later.
I got used to it.
I eventually realized how safe life vests are.
There was no one else around,
so swimming in the river was nice.
I think it was my first time
swimming in a valley like that.
It was quite peaceful.
[Even Jin Young, who's afraid of water]
It really was.
Let's all put on our sunglasses.
[A beautiful and peaceful time together]
Sun Jae, try lying down there.
- It was fun.
- Yeah.
Jumping off was a bit scary, though...
I remember Bo Gum jumping.
- Climbing up there.
- I just couldn't do it right.
[Wanna Be]
[Reality]
[Chairman Park's unexpected clumsy moment]
He fell kind of like this.
- Didn't you jump on trampolines as a kid?
- Trampolines?
- You've never been on one?
- Not even once.
But on a trampoline, you can do this.
- People do it all the time.
- Like rolling around?
- You can do three or four flips.
- Really?
[Rolling down]
Come down now. Yes.
[Bouncing with pride]
- That's amazing. Like a gymnast.
- It's addictive.
- This is so delicious.
- That's your third one.
- Huh?
- How much do you weigh?
- Me? About 66 kg?
- Sixty-six?
- Yeah.
- That's crazy.
- You're so thin.
You're in such good shape.
I thought you'd be in the 70s.
- Really?
- I was 65 kg during Moonlight.
What? You were 65 kg back then?
But now I'm 73... 74... 75 kg.
[The number keeps going up...]
You're thin too.
I'm 76 kg.
[Actually, he's 76 kg]
To be honest, I'm 76 kg.
[Relatable: understating his weight]
Wow, and you said 66.
- Were you 17 back then?
- Yes.
Did it feel different when you turned 20?
We went to the KBS Drama Awards
to present an award.
Remember the Top Excellence Award?
I wore a light purple dress.
That was the day I turned 20.
[December 31st!]
It was the 31st.
[You Jung turned 20 in the waiting room]
Midnight passed while I was there.
I'll work hard like my seniors
to stand here one day.
Park Bo Gum, please announce the winner.
After that, I went to Itaewon with my mom
and sister and had a drink.
I cried because I didn't want to turn 20.
- Really?
- Why?
I was dying to become
an adult as soon as possible.
I was a bit scared of becoming an adult.
[After their long chat...]
[Soo Bin returns from the hospital]
Are you okay?
I don't think it's a big deal.
Was your ear weak to begin with?
Maybe it's because
I kept calling her a herbivore?
[The Five Are Reunited Upon Soo Bin's Return]
- Shall we start getting ready for dinner?
- Sure.
[Today's Menu: Baeksuk, Kimchi Jeon...]
Prepare the green onions and Baeksuk.
- There's not much to prep for Baeksuk, right?
- No, you just put everything in whole.
I think we just need to wash the chicken.
[Taking out the chicken first]
[Dong Yeon naturally takes charge of Baeksuk]
The chicken...
[Bo Gum & Soo Bin prep the rest]
- Should I open this? - Sure.
Can I peel the onion?
No, put it in whole.
- Can I peel it?
- Put them all in whole.
- Can I take off this packaging?
- No.
Can I take off this packaging?
No, put it in whole.
That's where the flavor comes from.
[They almost ate Baeksuk with plastic in it]
Put this in whole.
[Prep complete as per Chef You Jung's orders]
[Time to stuff the prepped chicken]
I should put the ginkgo nuts in first.
[Ginkgo nuts, chestnuts, jujubes]
[Baeksuk prep is done]
Now we just need to prep the vegetables.
- I'll go light the fire, everyone.
- Okay.
[The Baeksuk will cook in a cauldron outside]
Are you okay with lighting the fire?
- Why?
- Aren't you scared?
[Oh, please]
Since you're scared of water, fire is also...
- I'm strong against fire.
- It's the opposite.
[Jin Young & Soo Bin stack the firewood]
- Just throw it in.
- Just throw it in?
I think you can just throw it in.
Can I just throw it in?
Don't we need to stack it, Oppa?
- It probably won't matter.
- Really?
You seem a bit skeptical?
[She is indeed skeptical]
- Right? - Have you done this before?
- And...
- They look like they know how to cook.
Not at all, Oppa.
No? Not at all?
Will those two be okay?
I'm suddenly worried
about leaving them by the fire.
[Fire Jin Young takes out the torch]
[He lights it up with confidence]
- But it's actually already done.
- Eh, really?
[Success in just 3 seconds...?]
It's lit.
The fire caught on so well at once.
- Wow, it lit so well.
- That was simple.
[Immediately putting the ingredients in]
[Simmer for an hour and it's done]
Then we just boil it like this for an hour.
I'm all done, man.
[Fire Jin Young returns confidently]
That's amazing.
- As long as it's not water.
[Meanwhile, Main Chef You Jung]
[Slice up the chives and perilla leaves,
quickly making the seasoning]
- What's this?
- Scallion salad.
[Scallion salad with perilla leaves & chives]
I just added perilla leaves and chives.
Now we just need to put the kimchi on a plate.
It's in the fridge.
You used everything for the kimchi pancake?
Yes. I've prepared it all.
[One hour ago, during break time]
[Quietly peeling potatoes alone]
[Shredding the potatoes]
[You Jung prepared the pancake batter]
[Bo Gum joins her soon after]
[Kimchi pancake batter]
[They gave up their rest for their friends]
Should I take out the watermelon?
[Dinner prep is on track thanks to them]
I've prepared everything.
Is there anything else I should do?
[Only the pancakes are left]
No. I just need to fry the pancakes.
[Glancing]
[He rushes to get up and go outside...?]
[The cauldron is smoking like crazy]
Wait, is there a fire?
[Checking the chicken soup]
It's not boiling at all.
[Only smoke, the soup isn't cooking]
[Damp firewood prevents a proper fire]
The fire isn't strong. Maybe it's damp.
[Appearing with kindling]
Because it's humid.
[Focusing]
[Struggling to save the chicken soup]
[Passionate photographer captures the crisis]
[The struggle for the soup is documented]
Wow, it's much stronger than before.
No joke. It's finally burning well.
[Checking the soup]
It's boiling.
[The chicken soup finally starts to boil]
[You Jung is about to fry the pancakes]
But what should I do about this?
I want to turn on the one next to it too.
[Sweet Chairman Park helps immediately]
[Starting to fry the pancakes]
[Spreading the batter on the pan]
[Adding one more pan?]
[Cover it with a lid to keep it moist inside]
[10 Minutes Later]
Oh, it looks delicious.
[The potato pancake is crispy outside,
soft inside, and done]
[Sizzle]
[Kimchi pancakes are ready in a flash]
[A short break while the baeksuk boils]
[Soo Bin wants to play...]
Should I... play the accompaniment?
- Should I?
- Oh, you know how to play it?
[Sweet Chairman Park sits right at the piano]
Ready, set, go.
Oh.
Oh!
[Staring]
Why is the song so sweet?
[Soo Bin and Bo Gum's sweet ensemble]
The song is so sweet.
[The summer night ensemble ends]
Since it's summer, we should add red ginseng
to boost our health.
[A must-have for summer baeksuk]
Awesome!
I just need to add this?
Yes.
It's a real health food.
Exactly.
- It'll be so good for our health.
- I'm curious.
- About the taste.
- Let's get healthy.
Should we take the baeksuk out now?
[Will the baeksuk be a success?]
- Someone help me. - Okay.
It looks delicious.
[The baeksuk is cooked to perfection]
Wow, hey, it looks delicious.
Wow, it turned out better than I thought.
It's no joke. The broth is amazing.
[Taking out the impressive baeksuk]
Is the broth good?
Wow, this is the main dish.
[Placed in the center of the table]
It turned out so well. Amazing, right?
[10 years ago - The baeksuk Ra On made]
Here.
[The main menu for the 10th anniversary dinner]
Wow, it looks so good.
[The rest of the table is full too]
It's a real feast.
[You Jung's crispy pancakes and...]
You're so generous. How many did you fry?
[Scallions, the perfect match for baeksuk]
Invite the whole neighborhood.
[Bo Gum's spicy noodles & Jin Young's lamb]
Wow, it's so hearty.
[A feast prepared with great care]
Come on, let's eat.
- Sounds good.
- Let's sit.
- You worked so hard making this.
- Good job, everyone.
Well done.
- Let's eat.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Enjoy your meal.
Let's take a photo first.
[The five of them enjoy a baeksuk feast]
- Yes. - Okay.
Hurry and enjoy your meal.
I'll carve the baeksuk.
[Dong Yeon carves the chicken for everyone]
Yes, thank you.
[Picking out the biggest chicken leg]
No, it's okay.
- Chef.
- Thank you.
You have a leg, and our patient
should have one too.
[Sharing the baeksuk one by one]
But I'm fine without a leg.
[You Jung takes a bite first]
No, it's okay, really.
Wow, this baeksuk is so delicious.
It is, right?
[Bo Gum takes a bite off the bone]
It's good.
[Cleanly deboned]
So good.
- This is real health food.
- It's got everything.
[Dong Yeon tries it too.]
How's the broth?
Is it good?
I can stay up all night!
Really? That much?
[Deep exclamations unlike a 20-something]
Do you feel energized?
You sound like a real dad.
[Dad...?]
He was an uncle just this morning.
Wow, man, this is...
Seriously, try it. It makes you like this.
- But eating this baeksuk...
- Yeah.
Do you remember that line at Jahyeondang?
The one where we talk behind his back?
The Crown Prince.
[Lines that come to mind while eating]
The Crown Prince's nickname.
- What was it?
- Ddong-gung-jeon?
Do you know the Crown Prince's nickname?
[Lee Yeong | Flower Prince?]
Flower Prince?
[Byeong Yeon | Ddong-gung-jeon]
Ddong-gung-jeon.
I knew everyone knew about it.
Then what about the other one?
Half-human, half-beast.
That's right.
- Right, right.
- That was the funniest part for me.
Since Dong Yeon is laughing...
"Oh, you know how to laugh?"
"I thought there was something
wrong with your face."
Right, right.
[Byeong Yeon laughs for the first time]
"Is he really that vicious and greedy?"
Hey, seriously!
"You laughed? Well, I'll be."
"I thought there was something
wrong with your face."
"What does the back of the
Crown Prince's head look like?"
"It's quite a sight."
"I thought there was something
wrong with your face."
- Right, right.
- The lines are so good.
But back then, I felt so much
responsibility and pressure.
While filming the drama?
That's how I felt.
But back then, You Jung was so
accommodating and took good care of me.
I thought, "Even if it's hard, it won't be
as hard as it is for You Jung."
Because your character had to go through
so many emotional shifts.
But even then, she'd always give me
xylitol whenever she came to the set.
- She took such good care of people.
- I did?
Yes, you. Even though you were
probably having a harder time.
Right. That's why I felt like
she was more like an adult.
Like Dr. Oh Eun Young.
I think that's how she got
the nickname Dr. Oh Eun Young.
In my heart, Dong Yeon was always
such a playful character.
When I look back at how we were then,
Dong Yeon was always smiling.
[Dong Yeon never lost his smile]
So that really touched me.
I was really thankful back then.
I didn't have much time to prepare
before we suddenly started filming.
And since I had the most scenes with you,
I was so grateful that you made me
feel so comfortable.
But what I'm really thankful for is that
we practically lived on that set.
- We'd eat and wash at the bathhouse.
- Right, we'd wash at the sauna.
The dressing room was
on the second floor of the set.
[The dressing room where they napped]
We'd sleep there with the AC on...
And one time, Dong Yeon left me a letter.
I did? What did I write?
Should I show you the letter?
Why would you show that?
- You still have it?
- I still have it.
[Dong Yeon's letter, kept for 10 years]
"Hyung, I'm heading to Suwon now."
"You were sleeping so soundly like a baby
angel that I couldn't bear to wake you."
"We're parting for now, but we'll
definitely meet again."
"I love you. Thank you."
Parting for just a few days?
[Sad to part even for a moment]
It was probably only for a few hours.
[A sweltering summer night]
Wow, it really is hot. I need another shower.
That'll be my fourth shower today.
How did you shower four times?
- Once in the morning.
- After waking up.
- And then? After the water activities.
- After the water activities.
- And then you did it again?
- That's only the third time.
Is that so important?
I'm just saying I showered a lot.
Sorry, sorry.
[Snapping because of the heat]
I'm just hot right now.
Hahaha, sorry, sorry.
It's like watching a dating reality show.
[EXchange: Gurmi Edition]
EXchange.
If you hadn't asked how many times I
showered, we wouldn't be acting like this.
If you'd told me it was that important,
I would've apologized already.
Why are you bringing this up here?
Just say you're sorry.
Thank you for the meal.
[After a delightful meal]
[The air cools as night falls]
It's much better now.
- Yeah, compared to before.
- This is amazing.
Wait, what?
- Look at that!
- Why?
- Those are sky lanterns.
- Sky lanterns!
Where?
[Colorful lanterns awaiting the Gurmis]
They're so pretty.
Wow, I'm touched.
[One of the many famous scenes]
Dear Heavens,
[from ]
Please grant our village a bountiful harvest!
[The specially remembered night
of the Lantern Festival]
[The moment Lee Yeong and Ra On grew closer]
[The Gurmis gathered for the Lantern Festival]
The memories just keep coming back, seriously.
What's this?
What's going on?
[Bo Gum is suddenly handed a microphone...?]
Why?
- What is it?
- What's happening?
- What's this?
- Nice to meet you.
[What is this situation?]
Oh, what's this?
Should I stand up?
[Everyone is confused by the situation]
- Should I sit down?
- No, what is this?
- What is it?
- Yes.
- Live broadcast. Music...
- Music Bank?
No, no.
It's Gurmi Cantabile.
[A special event prepared by former MC Bo Gum]
I'm your surprise MC for today, Park Bo Gum.
[Full of anticipation]
Awesome!
The reason I'm holding
the microphone on this meaningful day
is because!
To celebrate the 10th anniversary of Gurmi...
I knew it.
- Exactly.
- I knew it.
[A special guest who came all this way?]
We have a very special guest here today.
When I heard who the guest was,
I thought, "Wow, they're coming?"
[Is it that surprising?]
Wow, they're coming?
Really?
- Is it Cheon Ho Jin?
- Really?
Cheon Ho Jin.
I was so nervous and excited.
Cheon Ho Jin!
I miss you, Cheon Ho Jin.
Now, the guest who will make Gurmi Cantabile
shine even brighter.
Please welcome them
with a big round of applause.
♫ I swallow my heart ♫
♫ Holding a white moonflower ♫
What? They're going to sing?
- Isn't that Gummy?
- Really?
[Who is this surprise guest?]
I think it's a duet.
I will not allow it.
[Reliving a classic scene]
She is my person.
Let's go.
I will not allow it.
She is my person.
[Behind-the-scenes stories after 10 years]
Did your head hit it?
I really liked this scene.
Do you still watch it by any chance?
- I think I watched it recently.
- Really?
[Honesty that never disappoints]
Exactly.
I felt so bad for Bo Gum in that scene.
Back then, the set felt like
it would last forever.
Since we'll have more time
together in the future...
Thank you.
[The Moonlight crew let loose at night]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Chairman Park gets his groove on]
[The Moonlight crew's endless night]
It's like wearing an old school uniform
after graduating.
[The crew returns to their 10-year-old looks]
We meet again after ten years.
The belt feels smaller than back then.
I think the clothes got bigger.
- I felt like we've matured.
- We have matured.
[The crew's special time travel begins]
It feels really strange.
What will the next ten years be like?